Finding aid to the Classes of 1891-1900 records CA.MS.01022
Smith College Archives
Classes of 1891-1900 records
1823-1997
Smith College Archives
Smith College. Class of 1891.
CA.MS.01022
98.042 linear feet (190 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for use without restriction beyond the standard terms and conditions of Smith College Special Collections.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Whenever donation information for a particular set of material is known, it is included in the finding aid below. However, a majority of the material was not formally accessioned and its origins are not currently known.
Arrangement
This collection brings together ten record groups that are arranged chronologically, one per graduating class. However, since some materials are placed in a class record group based on when they were created, and not by whom, materials relelvant to a class may exist in more than one series.
Related Materials
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes. These files, which are organized by class and are housed in the boxes numbered immnediately after each set of Class Records are not currently listed in any finding aid; contact Special Collections for more information.
Scope and Contents
The Classes of 1891-1900 records consist of individual class notes, examinations, papers and class letters, correspondence, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks as well as reunion materials of the same nature, all related to or dating from the time periods during which these classes were students at Smith College.
Smith College--Students.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.; Smith College. Class of 1892.; Smith College. Class of 1893.; Smith College. Class of 1894.; Smith College. Class of 1895.; Smith College. Class of 1896.; Smith College. Class of 1897.; Smith College. Class of 1898.; Smith College. Class of 1899.; Smith College. Class of 1900.; Smith College--Students.; Smith College--Alumni and alumnae.
- Class of 1891 Records, 1866-1997; 5.167 linear feet (12 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  The Class of 1891 was the thirteenth graduating class of Smith College.
  Scope and Contents
  The Class of 1891 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1891. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, correspondence, student's journals, publications, manuscripts, newspaper clippings, student's class notes, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1891.
  - Class of 1891: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1455, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1891: Collation, 1906 (Box 1455, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1891: Commencement (Box 1455, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1891: Commencement Music (Box 1455, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1891: Freshman Grind by 1890 (Box 1455, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1891: Groups, 1886-87; 1889-91 (Box 1455, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1891: Ivy Day (Box 1455, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1891: Ivy Day (Photographs) (Box 1455, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1891: Junior Prom, 1890 (Box 1455, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1891: Class Letters, 1898; 1915-17; 1921; 1924; 1945-46; 1948-52; undated (Box 1456, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1891: Publications, undated (Box 1456, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1891: Class Secretary's Records, 1890s-1950s (Box 1456, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1891: Class Supper, History, Prophecies (Box 1456, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1891: Class Photo Book (Box 1456, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1891: Reunions, 1911-12; 1916; 1921; 1924-25; 1931; 1941; 1946-48; undated (Box 1456, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1891: Reunion Songs, 1911; 1921; 1925; 1941; undated (Box 1456, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1891: Reunion Photographs, 1916; 1936; 1941; 1950; undated (Box 1456, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1891: Senior Dramatics (Box 1456, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1891: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) (Box 1456, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1891: Songs, 1941; undated (Box 1456, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1891: Sophomore Reception, 1887 (Box 1456, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1891: Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1889 (Box 1456, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1891: Class Supper (Box 1456, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1891: Abbot, Florence Hale (Photographs, etc), 1896; 1918; undated (Box 1457, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1891: Aikens, Mary Lydia (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1457, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1891: Allen, Grace Weston (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1891: Ames, Grace Edith, 1888; undated (Box 1457, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1891: Baird, Mary Ellen (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1891: Barbour, Amy Louise (Photographs) (Box 1457, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1891: Barri, Alice Hamilton, undated (Box 1457, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1891: Barton, Mary Catherine (Photographs) (Box 1457, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1891: Billings, Anna Hunt (Photographs, etc), 1866-1912; 1914; 1941; 1944 (Box 1457, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1891: Bixby, Ada Perry (Photographs) (Box 1457, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1891: Blanchard, Florence Adelia (Photographs), 1937; 1947 (Box 1457, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1891: Bliss, Helen Rockwell (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1891: Bogue, Stella Margaret (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1891: Booth, Mary Martyn (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1891: Bowman, Blanche Wetherell (Photographs), 1888 (Box 1457, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1891: Brown, Harriet Langdon (Photographs, etc), 1918; undated (Box 1457, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1891: Brown, Mary Belle (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1891: Bruce, Grace A. (Box 1457, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1891: Cadwallader, Edith Warner (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1891: Cary, Lucia Beecher (Photographs) (Box 1457, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1891: Cary, Lucia Beecher (Paper on Charles Lamb), undated (Box 1457, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1891: Chapman, Carita Atwill (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1891: Churchyard, Mary (Photographs, etc) (Box 1457, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1891: Clark, Edith Ethelyn (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1891: Clute, Alice, 1960; undated (Box 1457, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1891: Collar, Mary Sibyl (Box 1457, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1891: Comins, Ellen Nellie Maria, 1906-08; 1912; undated (Box 1457, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1891: De Normandie, Sylvia Yardley, 1963 (Box 1457, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1891: Dole, Catherine Augusta, 1924; undated (Box 1457, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1891: Dwight, Bertha W. (Photographs, Letters), 1887-88; 1953; undated (Box 1457, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1891: Dwight, Bertha Woolsey (Lecture Notes, History of French Revolution), 1890 (Box 1457, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1891: Dwight, Bertha Woolsey (Lecture Notes, English Literature), 1890; undated (Box 1457, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1891: Dwight, Bertha Woolsey (Lecture Notes, American Literature) (Box 1457, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1891: Dwight, Bertha Woolsey (Class Notes, French), undated (Box 1457, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1891: Fairbanks, Lucy, undated (Box 1457, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1891: Foster, Mary Louise (Box 1457, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1891: Franklin, Charlotte G. (Box 1457, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1891: Fuller, Susan Gertrude, 1912; 1916; 1928; undated (Box 1457, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1891: Garland, Olive Rosamond (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1891: Granger, Edith, 1904-05; 1919-20; 1925; 1927-28; 1932; 1941; 1957 (Box 1457, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1891: Greene, Helen F. (Correspondence, Alumnae Register), 1944-46 (Box 1457, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1891: Greene, Helen French (Correspondence and Articles), 1866; 1909; 1925; 1928; 1936; 1947-48; 1952-53 (Box 1457, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1891: Greene, Helen French (Photographs), 1885; undated (Box 1457, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1891: Greene, Helen French (Reminiscences of Margaret Storrs Grierson, '22), 1980 (Box 1457, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1891: Greene, Helen French (Will), 1948 (Box 1457, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1891: Gulliver, Eunice Henrietta (Photographs), undated (Box 1457, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1891: Gutmann, Gertrude Louise (Box 1457, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1891: Hastings, Dora Loomis, 1902 (Box 1458, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1891: Hewitt, Helen Witter (Photographs), 1890; undated (Box 1458, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1891: Hill, Ellen Elisabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1891: Hoysradt, Jessie (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1891: Husted, Mary Irving (Photographs) (Box 1458, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1891: Keyes, Bertha Anna (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1891: LaMonte, Annie I. (Scrapbook) (Box 1458.1)
  - Class of 1891: Lamprey, Eva Blanche (Photographs), 1888; 1890; undated (Box 1458, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1891: Lang, Mary Susan (Photographs, etc), 1887-88; 1890; 1938; 1961; 1964; 1980; undated (Box 1458, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1891: Lauriat, Susette Foster (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1891: Lord, Helen Augusta (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1891: Mead, Katharine Lois (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1891: North, Georgia Lincoln (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1891: Olmsted, Frances Elizabeth (Photographs), 1889 (Box 1458, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1891: Ordway, Fanny Blanche (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1891: Osgood, Alice Florella (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1891: Paul, Florence Helen (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1891: Peck, Carolyn (Photographs, etc), 1890-91; 1913; 1947; undated (Box 1458, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1891: Peirce, Helen (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1891: Phillips, Mary Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1891: Platt, Eloise Clara (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1891: Porter, Jeanne P. (Box 1458, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1891: Puffer, Ethel Dench (Box 1458, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1891: Rand, Grace (Box 1458, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1891: Raymond, Mary Elizabeth, 1932; 1937; 1950; 1996-97 (Box 1458, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1891: Rice, Helen Rebecca (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1891: Robinson, Annie Florence (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1891: Rogerson, Frances Rice (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1891: Sabin, Mary Sophia (Photographs, etc), 1961; undated (Box 1458, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1891: Sawin, Laura Etta, 1910 (Box 1458, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1891: Severens, Mabel (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen Burns (Photographs) (Box 1458, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen (Miscellaneous), 1941; undated (Box 1459, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen (Anthology, Poems), 1916-17; undated (Box 1459, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen (Manuscripts, etc), 1914; 1945; undated (Box 1459)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen (Manuscripts), undated (Box 1460)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen (Manuscripts), 1953; undated (Box 1461)
  - Class of 1891: Sherman, Ellen (Manuscripts), 1899; 1902; 1906; 1908-09; 1912; 1914-19; 1921-24; 1926-27; 1935-36; 1938-46 (Box 1462)
  - Class of 1891: Sherwood, Alice (Photographs, Letters), 1890; 1921; undated (Box 1458, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1891: Simmons, Adeline Gertrude (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1891: Skinner, Lilian, 1907; 1912-13; 1915; 1918; 1922; 1924-27; 1931 (Box 1458, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1891: Slaght, Ethelwyn Rebecca, 1893-94; 1897; undated (Box 1458, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1891: Smith, May Manning (Photographs) (Box 1458, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1891: Sterne, Alice Louie, 1910 (Box 1458, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1891: Stetson, Jennie (Photographs, etc), 1898; undated (Box 1458, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1891: Taylor, Caro Cushing, 1891-92? (Box 1458, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1891: Trowbridge, Cornelia Rogers (Photographs), 1901 (Box 1458, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1891: Waite, Constance Eliza, 1952 (Box 1458, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1891: Wallace, Janet Monroe (Box 1458, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1891: Wallace, Janet Monroe (Letters), 1887-1890; undated (Box 1463)
  - Class of 1891: Wallace, Janet Monroe (Letters), 1890-91; 1895 (Box 1464)
  - Class of 1891: Wallace, Janet Monroe (Student papers, Journal, Miscellaneous), 1881-89; 1895; 1915-16; 1925-26; 1929-30; 1933-38; 1940-42; 1944-48; 1978; undated (Box 1465)
  - Class of 1891: Whitehill, Clara Agnes (Photographs, etc), 1960; undated (Box 1458, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1891: Wilder, Matilda Sewell (Photographs), undated (Box 1458, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1891: Williams, Elizabeth Sprague (Photographs, etc), 1890; 1912; 1914; 1922-23; 1970; undated (Box 1458, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1891: Williams, Elizabeth Sprague, 1914; undated (Box 1458, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1891: Wilson, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1458, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1891: Wood, Mabel (Photographs, etc), 1898; 1936; 1949; 1951; undated (Box 1458, Folder 48)
- Class of 1892 Records, 1874-1970; 4.917 linear feet (10 containers)
  The Class of 1892 was the fourteenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1892 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1892. Types of materials include black and white photographs, correspondence, letters, diaries, scrapbooks, journals, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1892.
  - Class of 1892: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1466, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1892: Class Letters, 1891-92; 1930-32; 1940 (Box 1466, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1892: Commencement (Box 1466, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1892: Commencement Music (Box 1466, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1892: Freshman Grind by 1891 (Box 1466, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1892: Groups- First Year, 1888-89 (Box 1466, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1892: Groups- Second Year, 1889 (Box 1466, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1892: Groups- Junior Year with J. Stoddard, 1890-91 (Box 1466, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1892: Groups- Senior Year and Art Students (Box 1466, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1892: Groups- Small Groups, 1888; 1891; undated (Box 1466, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1892: History, 1889; undated (Box 1466, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1892: Ivy Day (Box 1466, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1892: Junior Prom, 1891 (Box 1466, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1892: Parties, 1891-92; undated (Box 1466, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1892: Questionnaire (Box 1466, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1892: Records, 1888-97; 1902; 1907; 1910; 1912; 1916-17; 1920-22; 1925-27; 1932; 1937; 1941-42 (Box 1466, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1892: Reunions, 1913; 1916; 1925; 1927; 1932; 1942; 1947 (Box 1467, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1892: Reunions- Owls (Box 1467, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1892: Reunion Photographs, 1907; 1912-1913; 1947; undated (Box 1467, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1892: Reunion Songs, 1902; 1912; 1927; 1932; undated (Box 1467, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1892: Reunion- 1937 (Box 1467, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1892: Reunion- 1962 (Box 1467, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1892: Reunion Memorabilia (Box 1467.1)
  - Class of 1892: Seal (Box 1467, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1892: Senior Dramatics- Music (Box 1467, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1892: Senior Dramatics- Photographs (Box 1467, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1892: Senior Dramatics- Programs (Box 1467, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1892: Songs (Box 1467, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1892: Sophomore Reception, 1888 (Box 1467, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1892: Class Supper (Box 1467, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1892: Adams, Helena Belle, undated (Box 1468, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1892: Austin, Martha, 1898-1900; 1902; 1906-08; 1932-33 (Box 1468, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred, 1895; 1915; 1926 (Box 1468, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred (Diary, Sept. 1888-Sept.1889), 1888-89 (Box 1469.1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred (Diary, Sept. 1891-Mar. 1892), 1891-92 (Box 1469.1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred (Diary, Mar. 1892-Aug. 1892) (Box 1469.1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred (Diary, Jan. 1894-Dec. 1894) (Box 1469.1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1469.1)
  - Class of 1892: Ayres, Winifred (Scrapbook- loose items), 1883; 1885; 1889; 1893-97; 1899; 1902; undated (Box 1469.1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1892: Blanchard, Helen Train (Photographs) (Box 1468, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1892: Boyd, Harriet Ann, 1900-01; 1904-05 (Box 1468, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1892: Bridges, Eliza Wadsworth McMechan (Photographs), 1891 (Box 1468, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1892: Brown, Edith B. (Photographs, etc), 1897; 1902; 1912; undated (Box 1468, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1892: Burnham, Mary Eunice Lord (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1892: Charles, Pauline, undated (Box 1468, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1892: Clark, Edith Lucia (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1892: Coolidge, Cora H., 1924; 1931; 1954; undated (Box 1468, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1892: Crehore, Mary Louise (Photographs, etc), 1894; undated (Box 1468, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1892: Crofoot, Sara Elizabeth, undated (Box 1468, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1892: Curtis, Elnora Whitman, 1908-10; 1913 (Box 1468, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1892: Cushman, Ruth G. (Diaries), 1889-92 (Box 1468, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1892: Cushman, Ruth G. (Letters, etc), 1888; 1890-91 (Box 1468, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1892: Cushman, Ruth Gilman (Photographs) (Box 1468, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1892: Cutler, Eleanor Evelyn (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1892: De Land, Helen Parce, 1951 (Box 1468, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1892: Dennen, Grace Atherton (Journals- The Ebell, The Lyric West), 1898-99; 1922 (Box 1470, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1892: Dennen, Grace Atherton (Journals- The Lyric West), 1921-22 (Box 1470, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1892: Drew, Marion (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1892: Folsom, Martha Thayer (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1892: Francis, Vida Hunt (Photographs, etc), 1912-13; 1922 (Box 1468, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1892: Gilbert, Clara Culver (Photographs) (Box 1468, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1892: Goodwin, Sarah (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1892: Haven, Katherine Lillian, 1908; undated (Box 1468, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1892: Hawks, Emma, 1894 (Box 1468, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1892: Henshaw, Mary Dana (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1892: Hogan, Lucy Mary, undated (Box 1468, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1892: Howland, Elisabeth Collamore (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1892: Hungerford, Katherine (Photographs), undated (Box 1468, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1892: Jacobs, Harriet Ethel (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1892: Jordan, Mary Adela (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1469, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1892: Kerruish, Miriam Gertrude, 1901 (Box 1469, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1892: Kilbon, Amelia Jeanette (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1892: Kimball, Martha Smith, 1964-65 (Box 1469, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1892: Langworthy, Jessica L., 1931-32; 1936; 1938; 1947; 1970 (Box 1469, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1892: Learoyd, Elizabeth Abbot (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1892: Learoyd, Elizabeth Abbot (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1471)
  - Class of 1892: Learoyd, Elizabeth Abbott (Scrapbooks) (Box 1471.4, Box 1471.3)
  - Class of 1892: Lord, Grace (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1892: Lyon, Louise, 1874-75; 1877; undated (Box 1469, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1892: MacDougall, Margaret (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1892: McConway, Laura- Art Student (Group Photo) (Box 1469, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1892: McConway, Laura- Art Student (Miscellaneous), 1888-91; undated (Box 1469, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1892: McMillan, Frances (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1892: Mitchell, Eliza Lamb (Photographs), 1902 (Box 1469, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1892: Nichols, Fanny Augusta, 1891 (Box 1469, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1892: Nichols, Helen Christine, undated (Box 1469, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1892: Nixon, Mary Stites (Photographs, etc), 1911-12; undated (Box 1469, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1892: Parsons, Harriet, undated (Box 1469, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1892: Pratt, Elsie Fay (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1892: Pratt, Grace Tyler, 1922 (Box 1469, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1892: Putney, Carrie Maria (Photographs, etc), 1891; undated (Box 1469, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1892: Rankin, Mary Poland, undated (Box 1469, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1892: Richards, Martha Billings, 1917-18; 1949 (Box 1469, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1892: Rowley, Helen A., undated (Box 1469, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1892: Safford, Anne Williston (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1892: Sands, Helen Elizabeth (Photographs) (Box 1469, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1892: Searl, Irlavere Jane (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1892: Seaver, Etta Anne (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1892: Shepard, Lillian Estella (Photographs), 1891; undated (Box 1469, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1892: Shipman, Carolyn (Photographs), 1900; 1912-13; undated (Box 1469, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1892: Smith, Bertha Linton (Correspondence), 1891 (Box 1469, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1892: Smith, Bertha Linton (Photographs), 1889-92; 1898; undated (Box 1469, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1892: Smith, Mary Shannon, 1890; 1893; undated (Box 1469, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1892: Steele, Caroline Lounsbury (Photographs) (Box 1469, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1892: Stoddard, May Baldwin (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1892: Twitchell, Julia Curtis (Box 1469, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1892: Tyler, Lena Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1892: Underwood, Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1469, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1892: Veeder, Jessie Budington (Photographs) (Box 1469, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1892: Walbridge, Wilhelmina von Colson (Photographs), 1890 (Box 1469, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1892: Wallin, Madeleine (Box 1469, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1892: Waterman, Patty Lee, 1905; 1916 (Box 1469, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1892: Wheeler, Blanche Emily, 1936 (Box 1469, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1892: Wild, Laura Huldah, 1898; 1913; 1916; 1921-23; 1930; undated (Box 1469, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1892: Williams, Helen Rachel (Box 1469, Folder 45)
- Class of 1893 Records, 1886-1995; 6.958 linear feet (13 containers)
  The Class of 1893 was the fifteenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1893 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1893. Types of materials include black and white photographs, photo albums, correspondence, letters, scrapbooks, class notes, newspaper clippings, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1893.
  - Class of 1893: Collation (Box 1472, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1893: Commencement (Box 1472, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1893: Commencement Music (Box 1472, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1893: Commencement Photographs (Box 1472, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1893: Groups, 1889-93 (Box 1472, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1893: Groups, 1889-91; undated (Box 1472, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1893: History, undated (Box 1472, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1893: Ivy Day (Box 1472, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1893: Ivy Day Photographs (Box 1472, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1893: Junior Prom, 1892 (Box 1472, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1893: Class Letters, 1910; 1912; 1914-19; 1922-33 (Box 1472, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1893: Fund Letters, 1930; 1936 (Box 1472, Folder 12)